usapoliticstoday.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy | USA Politics Today

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of USA Politics Today (“we,” or “us”). Generally, you may visit the Site without giving us any information about yourself. However, there are times when we may need to obtain personal information from you in order to provide certain services that you may request.  
USA Politics Today respect your right to privacy and treat the personal information you provide to us with the utmost care. Unless you indicate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time of collection, all personal information you provide to us will remain strictly between USA Politics Today and yourself.  
Each time a visitor comes to our website, we collect some basic information, including the visitor’s ISP (e.g. AOL, Comcast, or AT&T), referring site (e.g. Google, Facebook, or Yahoo) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Chrome browser on a Windows platform).  
We may collect personal information, including your name, cell phone number, email address, and certain demographic data, only when you choose to voluntarily provide to us such information, such as by subscribing to a newsletter, making inquiries regarding our services, requesting breaking news alerts, reporting any problems with our Site, participating in a promotional offer, providing us with feedback on our Site, or otherwise.  
We also track visitors’ activity on our sites. We may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may be shared on an aggregate basis with our advertisers.  
Contact Us:  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at webmaster@usapoliticstoday.com
